let's look at the solution to our
write-update coherence quiz where what
we had is for access is like this
happening in a write-update
coherent set of caches after the first
read completes here we have data six
tags 700 hex and the valid bit is 1 so
when this read completes we have a valid
bit 1 here the data is 6 and the tag is
700 at that time in these other caches
the valid bit is simply 0 because they
have not accessed anything yet
when core 1 reads it sets the valid bit
and fetch is the same data when quarto
writes it broadcasts the value in the
address so these caches that already
have this block will update what they
have now 217 and now of course on core
to this block starts being valid and has
a value of 17 and finally when core tree
reads it also gets the value of 17 so
this is the final state of the caches
all caches have the block and all caches
have the same value of the block which
means that really the caches are
coherent for this block